Finding Aid for the Fremont Ackerman Papers LSC.0312
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Western Heights--Western Avenue & Washington Street, Los Angeles County., 1904.; 1 item. (Box 116)
- Westlake Park Tract--Westlake Avenue & Orange Street, Los Angeles., 1924.; 1 item. (Box 123)
- Westland Tract--Main Street & 80th Street, Los Angeles., 1 item. (Box 156)
- Westland Tract--Moneta Avenue & 79th Street, Los Angeles County., 1907.; 1 item. (Box 116)
- White's Fourth Street Tract--boundary--Matthews Street, Los Angeles County., 1936.; 1 item. (Box 111)
- Whittier--Proposed annex no.2 of Los Angeles County., 1929.; 2 items. (Box 104)
- Whittier Boulevard / Workman Mill Road, Los Angeles County., 1924.; 1 item. (Box 83)
- Whittier Road, Los Angeles County., 1926.; 9 items. (Box 74)
- Wildwood Lodge, San Bernardino County., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 153)
- Wilmington Street in Rancho San Pedro, Los Angeles County., 1917.; 2 items. (Box 76)
- Wilshire--Harvard Heights (E.A. Forrester & Sons), Los Angeles., 1905.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Wilshire Boulevard & Lucerne Boulevard, Los Angeles County., 1925.; 5 items. (Box 76)
- Wilshire Boulevard Heights--Westlake District, Los Angeles., n.d.; 2 items. (Box 156)
- Wilshire Boulevard Heights--Wilshire Boulevard & Catalina Street, Los Angeles., 1904.; 5 items. (Box 123)
- Wilshire Boulevard Tract--Wilshire Boulevard & Coronado Street, Los Angeles., 1897.; 1 item. (Box 118)
- Wilson Tract--Central Avenue / Jefferson Street, Los Angeles., n.d.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Windsor Square--promotional brochure illustrated with photographs, Los Angeles., 1 item. (Box 156)
- Winsor Tract no.2--Cleveland Avenue, Los Angeles County., 1905.; 1 item. (Box 117)
- Wolfskill Property, Los Angeles County., n.d.; 6 items. (Box 138)
- Woollacott Tract--First Street / Clarence Street, Los Angeles., 1895.; 1 item. (Box 156)
- Woolley's Subdivision of lot 49--Watts' Subdivision, Los Angeles County., 1885.; 1 item. (Box 108)
- Workman Ranch & Canfield Estate Property--Wright Road & Downey and Florence Road, Los Angeles., 1925, 1927.; 3 items. (Box 127)
- Wright (C.M.) Tract--Plat, Los Angeles., 1901.; 3 items. (Box 109)
- Yorba Linda Tract--J.C. Belton lot, Yorba Linda., 1931.; 1 item. (Box 121)
- Young (William) property--23rd Street & Union Avenue, n.p., 1913.; 1 item. (Box 111)
- Zamora & 102nd Street, Los Angeles County., 1931.; 24 items. (Box 99)